Densho: Japanese American Incarceration and Japanese Internment

* Search for:  

Densho: Japanese American Incarceration and Japanese Internment

Search for:  

Terms of Use / Privacy Policy
=============================

Terms of Use
------------

### Warranties

Densho does not make any warranty whatsoever, including without limitation: that any and all of its website properties including, but not limited to: www.densho.org, ddr.densho.org, encyclopedia.densho.org and resourceguide.densho.org (“Densho sites”), will be uninterrupted or error-free; that defects will be corrected; that the sites, including the servers that makes them available, are free of viruses or other harmful components; as to the results that may be obtained from use of the material on the sites; or as to the accuracy, reliability, availability, suitability, quality, or operation of any information, software, or service provided on or accessible from the Densho sites.

Densho sites and all information, products, and content included or accessible from Densho’s website properties are provided “as is” and without warranties of any kind (express, implied, and statuatory, including but not limited to the warranties of title and non-infringement and the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose), all of which Densho disclaims to the fullest extent permitted by law. Your use of Densho sites is at your sole risk.

### Limits of Liability

In no event shall Densho be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, punitive or consequential damages arising out of or related to the use, inability to use, authorized use, performance or nonperformance of the Densho sites, even if Densho was previously advised of the possibility of such damages and regardless of whether such damages arise in contract, tort, under statute, in equity, at law or otherwise.

Privacy Policy
--------------

Your privacy is important to Densho. Our Privacy Policy is your assurance of our commitment. The www.densho.org website, and other related properties published under the densho.org domain, including ddr.densho.org, encyclopedia.densho.org and resourceguide.densho.org, are owned and operated by Densho, a Washington State not-for-profit corporation. Our physical address is:

> Densho  
> 1416 S. Jackson St.  
> Seattle, WA 98144  
> US

Please feel free to contact us with any questions or comments regarding this policy.

### Personal Information

Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, usage data, along with the name, telephone number, address, and e-mail address. Densho collects information from our users at several different points on our website:

### **Comments and Feedback**

Densho’s sites provide a number of ways for users to communicate with us and others who may use the site. The contact form and blog comment form collect the information you choose to submit, including your name, email and question/comment. In addition, the server software provides us with the time you submitted the form and your computer’s IP address.

### **Densho eNews**

The Densho eNews is an optional monthly bulletin sent to people interested in Densho and related activities. Individuals opt-in to subscribe at the Densho website or through personal contact. Subscribers may choose to unsubscribe at any time. Unsubscribe information is located at the bottom of each eNews. Densho uses the [Mailchimp](https://mailchimp.com/) service to send and manage the email list.

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small packet of information that Densho puts on your computer’s hard drive whenever a user visits our website. For each visitor to our website, our server automatically recognizes the following:

* Your computer’s IP address
* How you were referred to the site
* The pages you have viewed
* Browser type (e.g., Firefox)
* Platform dependent information (e.g., Windows 10)
* Session data, which includes successful login. This state is closed upon closing the browser.
* Densho also uses Google Analytics to analyze traffic to this website. These analytic services do not create individual profiles for visitors. They collect only aggregate data. For more information about Google Analytics, click [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en).

### **Server logs**

The server software that powers Densho’s sites automatically record information about the requests for pages, images and other data made by your web browser. This includes IP address, what page or item was requested, and when the request was made.

### How the Information is Used

Information collected through the contact form and direct feedback email is used to answer the questions and inquiries submitted by the user.

Cookies are used to monitor the traffic on our website so we can keep track of which pages are most frequently visited, and to allow users to go from page to page without re-entering browsing preferences.

Server logs help us to analyze and forecast the resources necessary to run the sites, and troubleshoot technical problems when they arise.

Comments are used to revise, correct, update, and evaluate the content of our website.

### Information Sharing

Densho does not sell, rent, swap or otherwise disclose any personal information to third parties. If Densho is required to disclose information collected from our members in response to any legal process issued by a court, Densho will comply with the legal process after giving notice to any members affected by it unless a court order prohibits such notice.

x

Stay informed with Densho updates
---------------------------------

First Name

Last Name

Email

Comments

This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Copyright © 2024 Densho

Remembering the past, investing in our future

Donations made throughout our spring campaign will be matched up to $50,000](https://densho.donorsupport.co/-/XYJVGLUB)

x
